'use strict';

const words = [
  {question: 'Sul Sul', answer: 'Hello'},
  {question: 'Dag Dag', answer: 'Goodbye'},
  {question: 'Hooba Noobie', answer: 'What\'s up'},
  {question: 'Litzergam', answer: 'Thank you'},
  {question: 'Geelfrob', answer: 'See you soon'},
  {question: 'Whippna Choba Dog', answer: 'This is cool'},
  {question: 'Boobasnot', answer: 'I don\'t like you'},
  {question: 'Cuh Teekaloo', answer: 'How\'s it going'},
  {question: 'Renato', answer: 'Go away'},
  {question: 'Jowlenin', answer: 'Interesting'},
  {question: 'Kooj', answer: 'Sweet'},
];


const SLL =[
  {head: {value: {question: 'Sul Sul', answer: 'Hello'}, next: SLL[1],}},
  {value: {question: 'Dag Dag', answer: 'Goodbye'}, next: SLL[2]}
];